Full Fashioned Hosiery Industry Arbitration Documents and Publications 6090
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Full Fashioned Hosiery Industry Arbitration Documents and Publications
1929- 1939
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Full Fashioned Hosiery Industry
6090
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5793335
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective labor agreements -- Hoisery industry; Arbitration, Industrial; Abelson, Paul; Taylor, George W.
5793335
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman Series A Sept. 1929- July 1930, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series A, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Paul Abelson
    Notes: September 1929 - July 1930
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Decisions of Impartial Chairman: Series B Sep. 1930 - Feb. 1931, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series B, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: September 1930 - February 1931
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series C Mar. - June 1931, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series C, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: March - June 1931.
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series D June. - Aug. 1931, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. D, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: June - August 1931
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series E Oct. 1931 - July 1932, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series E, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: George W. Taylor
    Notes: October 1931 - July 1932,
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman. Series F Sept. 1932 - Dec. 1933, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series F, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 1932 - December 1933.
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman. Series G Jan. 1934- Jan. 1935, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series G, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: January 1934 - January 1935.
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman. Series H Jan. 1935 - Mar. 1936, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series H, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: January 1935 - March 1936.
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series J Apr. 1936 - Oct. 1936 Series K Aug. 1937 - Sep. 1938, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series J, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: April - October 1936.
  - Item 2: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series K, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 1937 - September 1938.
- Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series L Oct. 1938 - Dec. 1939, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Full Fashion Hosiery Industry National Labor Agreement. Decisions of the Impartial Chairman: Series L, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: George W. Taylor; Willima E. Simkin
    Notes: October 1938 - December 1939.
- Handbook of Decision Principles 1947, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Handbook of Decision Principles of the Impartial Chairman Dr. G. W. Taylor, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Author: George W. Taylor; R. F. Peden